NONT SUMATE

Front-end Developer

ABOUT ME

Experienced IT Support Engineer with over two years of success in addressing diverse challenges, specializing in basic networking., router and switch configuration, IT help desk operations, Microsoft 365, and Linux essentials. A skilled Front-end Developer and Web Design Developer proficient in H HTML CSS, JavaScript, Photoshop, and Python foundation in machine learning. Actively engaged in AI and Azure labs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Jan 2019- 2023 Snack2rock Co.,Ltd.l Bangkok, Thailand

Managing Director

- -Proven ability to develop and execute strategic business plans, resulting in expansion into new markets and increased profitability.
- -Built strong relationships with key c customers, including supplier and strategic opportunities and sustainable partners, resulting in increased business partnerships.

2012 - 2015 Tom N Toms Coffee | Bangkok, Thailand

Operation Manager

-Led high-performing teams. Contributed to financial analysis.

Managed day-to-day operations for a team of 20 employees, ensuring smooth workflow and productivity.

 * -Implemented and streamlined processes and procedures, resulting in a 20% increase in efficiency.

2009 - 2012 Source Code Co.,Ltd. | Bangkok, Thailand

IT Support engineer

- *- Provided end-user tr. r training and documentation to improve IT literacy and reduce repeat support requests.
- · Collabora rated with cross-fun functional teams to deploy and maintain enterprise-widesoftware and hardware solutions.

RECENTLY CERTIFICATION

 Career Essentials in Generative Al by Microsoft and Linkedin Career Essentials in Generative Al by Microsoft and Linkedin

04 11 920 061

- noniesatanegmail.com
- www.nontsumate.com
- 169 llivingstone Rd. Marrickville, Sydney, NSW 12204

EDUCATION

Certificate IV (IT Networking) TAFE NSW

Bachelor of Business and administrator (IT) Assumption University 1997-2002

EXPERTISE

Web Design, HTML, CSS

JAVASCRIPT

TYPESCRIPT

REACT

PHP

LANGUAGE

English

Thai